Hello everyone. This is Dan from Smoke
Cartel here in the Angeles National
Forest.
And we're out here because we're trying
out the V Labs Halo eRig. The Halo is
electronic, which means that you can
charge it up and bring it all the way
out to bum nowhere. The Halo has three
temperature settings. You can set it to
480°, 600°, or 750° Fahrenheit. Instead
of using a kanthal coil, which is what
we traditionally see, it uses something
called a nichrome coil. Unless you're a
coil cobbler,
the only real thing that you need to
worry about in terms of the difference
between the two is that nichrome heats
up faster. It comes with this glass
bubbler, which slides right into the
silicone track here. And that brings up
an interesting point with these eRigs
that do combine the electronic elements
with the handmade glass portion. Your
glass bubbler is going to be different
than every other glass bubbler that was
ever sent out because it's hand-crafted.
You're getting the electronic precision
with the artisanal elements of a
hand-crafted glass piece all in one. So,
the advantage is that you would get if
you bought a rig that was made by hand
throughout every
A bee just landed on me.
Okay. Okay, I'm just going to do this as
if I Okay. You're getting a piece of
You're getting
vibes.
Okay. Oh, thank god. This glass piece
has the seven-hole percolation with two
recycler chambers. That's why this
bubbler is ideal. The water and vapor
can move around twice within that small
space. You want filtration, but you
don't want too much diffusion. You want
to preserve the terpenes because they're
more fragile. And that's what makes the
Halo so special, I think. It takes
pretty much every innovation that has
led us up to this point in the smoking
industry, and it puts it all into one
device that you can literally hold in
your hand and take to the top of a
[\h__\h] mountain. So, check it out on
our website smokecartel.com.